1. What happens when a file is deleted in the main branch and updated in a feature branch, and how is this handled during a merge?

When a file is deleted in main branch and is updated in feature branch it results in a conflict while merging the two if given changes are committed, rather it won't affect the merge until the changes are actually committed. Hence the conflict is to be resolved by making changes in either of the branches and merge again, solving the issue.