Q3. Under what conditions will Git consider a file that has been deleted as being renamed, and what criteria does Git use to determine that a new file is a renamed version of the deleted file?

Git considers a file that is deleted being renamed if there is a new file added in the staging area that has content matching with the initial file. Here, the file extension doesn't matter if the content of files matches. The content of the new file and deleted file should match at least 50% to determine that the new file is a renamed version of the deleted file or else the new file will be considered as a newly added file and deleted as a normally removed/deleted file.